<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-29T17:28:54-06:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Brunch Tradition</title><subtitle>The Heritage of Food</subtitle><entry><title type="html">French Toast</title><link href="/recipes/2020/06/25/french-toast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="French Toast" /><published>2020-06-25T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-25T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/06/25/french-toast</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/06/25/french-toast.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/french-toast.png&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;recipe&quot;&gt;Recipe&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 Large Eggs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Cup Milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Tablespoon Honey or Sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pinch of Nutmeg&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pinch of Cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Butter for Frying&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;White bread&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maple Syrup for serving (I like Kirkland)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heat a skillet to medium&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whisk eggs and add the Milk, Honey or sugar, Nutmeg, and Cinnamon. Continue whisking until all ingredients are well combined.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Submerge bread in egg mixture for about 5 seconds on each side. Allow excess egg to drip before placing on the heated, buttered skillet. Repeat this step for the rest of the bread.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tip: If cooking for a large gathering, place a plate in an oven heated to 200° Fahrenheit and add finished French Toast to the plate until all the French Toast is made and you are ready to eat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/french-toast.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/french-toast.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Creation of Eggs Benedict and the Perfect Brunch Dish</title><link href="/recipes/2020/06/20/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Creation of Eggs Benedict and the Perfect Brunch Dish" /><published>2020-06-20T20:20:13-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-20T20:20:13-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/06/20/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/06/20/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish.png&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The origins of eggs Benedict are a bit of a mystery, although it’s believed to have at least originated in New York City during the Gilded Age. There are two main conflicting versions of who came up with the popular combination of poached eggs and Canadian bacon on a toasted English muffin with hollandaise sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first account credits the creation of eggs Benedict to Chef Charles Ranhofer in 1860. Ranhofer was the chef at Delmonico’s Restaurant, the first ever restaurant opened in the United States. It’s said that one of Delmonico’s regular patrons, Mrs. LeGrand Benedict, wanted something new to eat for lunch. She was so familiar with Delmonico’s menu that she had a discussion with Ranhofer to help switch things up, and then he created the recipe for eggs Benedict. His recipe even shows up in a cookbook he published in 1894 called The Epicurean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other version of the story claims eggs Benedict was created by a man named Lemuel Benedict in 1894. It’s said that after an evening of heavy partying, Lemuel Benedict went to the Waldorf Hotel for brunch where he invented a new sandwich by ordering a poached egg with bacon on buttered toast and a hooker of hollandaise sauce. His hangover cure supposedly caught the eye of the Waldorf’s renowned chef, Oscar Tschirky, who made a few adjustments to Lemuel’s original recipe by swapping ham for the bacon and an English muffin for toast. The creation was added to the Waldorf’s menu and has been a brunch fixture ever since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other theories suggest that Tschirky, who worked at Delmonico’s before switching to the Waldorf, may have stolen the recipe from Ranhofer and served it to his own patrons. It’s uncertain which story is true since there is not much evidence to back up either claim. For a while, the LeGrand Benedict story was the more widely believed version of events. That is until Jack Benedict, the son of Lemuel Benedict’s cousin, began advocating for the other story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jack was convinced Lemuel Benedict was the true inventor of eggs Benedict. He regularly advocated for Lemuel’s version of events and became quite upset when a 1978 article in Bon Appetit magazine credited LeGrand Benedict as the founder of the dish. It became part of Jack’s life mission to restore Lemuel’s story and make sure his relative was credited with the creation of the popular brunch dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jack even opened a restaurant named L. C. Benedict Restaurant and Tavern. In his establishment, Jack served eggs Benedict two ways. The first was the popular version we see today with Canadian bacon and an English muffin, and the second was Lemuel’s “original” version of buttered toast and bacon. Jack even sent a business proposal to McDonald’s encouraging the chain to create a breakfast sandwich called Eggs McBenedict that would accompany detailed placemats featuring an image of Lemuel himself. This partnership never went through, but Jack’s dedication to his cause did ultimately bring more attention to Lemuel’s story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it’s difficult to say for certain who really created eggs Benedict, we can all be grateful that it exists today. The combination of puffy poached eggs on a crispy toasted muffin along with the creamy hollandaise sauce and salty Canadian bacon is the perfect treat during any brunch outing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;recipe&quot;&gt;Recipe&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hollandaise Sauce For 1 Serving, multiply by the amount of servings required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Egg Yolk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Tablespoons Unsalted Butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lemon Juice to Taste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cayenne Pepper to Taste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salt to Taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add about an inch of water to a sauce pan and bring to a low simmer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whisk egg yolk(s) in a bowl until they are very well combined. If your eggs are right out of the fridge, you may want to briefly put them over the simmering water to heat them up slightly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place bowl over the simmering water and continue to whisk until the eggs have slightly thickened.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add the butter to the mixture 1 tablespoon at a time, whisking until each piece is incorporated. Continue whisking until the sauce is to your desired consistency.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whisk in Lemon Juice, Cayenne Pepper, and Salt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eggs Benedict&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;English Muffin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Pieces of Thinly Sliced Ham&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Poached Eggs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Diced Green Onion/Spring Onion/Scallion&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Smoked Paprika to Taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Poach the Eggs. Yolks should be runny.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Toast the English Muffin in a toaster or in a pan with a little bit of butter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heat Ham slices in a pan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place 1 Ham Slices on each half of the toasted English Muffin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place 1 Poached Egg on each Ham Slice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top each egg with about 1 Tablespoon of the Hollandaise Sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sprinkle Paprika on top.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish by garnishing with green onions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/the-creation-of-eggs-benedict-and-the-perfect-brunch-dish.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Steak and Eggs</title><link href="/recipes/2020/05/14/steak-and-eggs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Steak and Eggs" /><published>2020-05-14T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-14T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/05/14/steak-and-eggs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/05/14/steak-and-eggs.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/steak-and-eggs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine this. You wake up bright and early in the morning. The sun is out, just peeking over the horizon but enough to wake you from a deep night’s sleep. There is a powerful aroma floating through the air. You inhale deeply, awakening your sense of smell and taste as the aroma becomes more apparent. What is that delicious scent? Suddenly the realization hits you, and you smile, knowing there is a drool-worthy dish waiting for you in the kitchen; it can only be steak and eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up as a child- even into adolescence- my family always valued the beautiful, succulent combination of steak and eggs. Steak is a rich cut of meat that, when cooked just right, can bring on an otherworldly array of flavor. This is also true for eggs that are cooked fresh from the market- or even from the farm if you raise your own chickens. One can only be so lucky. The flavors in the steak pair wonderfully with eggs because they are both considered “bases” that can be built upon with side items and garnishes. When cooked in unison, they mix almost too smoothly, but what is the origin of this traditional combination?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The history of how this dish became a staple in many households is quite interesting. Let us take a brief trip into the past, starting in the 1950s – 1970s. This was a time in American culture when eating healthy portions of protein was a top priority for the common man/woman. Scarfing down meat and eggs at any time of day meant health, wealth, and survival. Nutrition was not so much a concern as it is in 2020, but this is no surprise since going to sleep with a full belly at the end of a long work-day overshadowed any concept of “going green” or relying on salad to stay satiated. Nevertheless, a shift began to take place in the diet world, and regularly consuming hearty meals like steak and eggs were better left to athletes and bodybuilders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On May 5, 1961, a game-changer occurred that cemented steak and eggs into American history. NASA astronaut Alan Shephard decided he needed a low-maintenance meal filled with loads of protein to keep him full throughout his flight into space that day. He woke up, ate a filling meal of steak and eggs, and then launched himself into space. Since then, NASA has adopted the dish as their traditional, legendary breakfast of choice. History speaks for itself; this dish truly is a foundation in American cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, no matter if you are an athlete, astronaut, or accountant, everyone can enjoy the full-flavored experience of this meal. While it might not be a dish eaten every day, it is definitely worth splurging on for Sunday brunch or a date-night with your loved one. Not only is it delicious, but it is also easy to whip up, adding your own personal twist with garnishes and seasonings. I hope you enjoy mastering this steak and eggs recipe no matter the decade, time of day, or location (yes, outer space counts). Now, let’s get to cooking.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/steak-and-eggs.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/steak-and-eggs.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Crepes From The Good Old Days</title><link href="/recipes/2020/05/07/crepes-from-the-good-old-days.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crepes From The Good Old Days" /><published>2020-05-07T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-07T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/05/07/crepes-from-the-good-old-days</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/05/07/crepes-from-the-good-old-days.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/crepes-from-the-good-old-days.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time flies. Seasons pass so fast, yet memories last so long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up as an American kid was great and really fun. There are so many memories to point out to, but one has always stood out—and that’s a story I cannot narrate without tagging my mother. So, that was about my mornings. Yes, the great breakfasts she would make for us. Coming from the middle-class American society, I can almost conclude that my story relates to most of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the earliest days of the United States, days of the great tradition, American families started their days with whatever was most readily available. Breakfasts could literally be anything ranging from a kale-and-almond-butter smoothie, Crab Imperial Chesapeake to Rainbow Brite and Mr. T novelty cereals. I’m pretty sure you 90’s kids really enjoyed them. These were great meals to bring the family together and kick-start the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, back to the main story. For most of us, if not all, our mothers are the most important people we can talk about. People you can always rest assured that they’ve got your back. The beautiful memories she made for us while growing up are still so alive in us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Holiday time is eating time,” my little dawg would say. And owing to the flavorsome meals our mother would make, he really did. Our most exciting holidays were Easter and Christmas—which I still enjoy up until today. These were the days to enjoy the most delicious meals away from school. Our breakfast, in particular, was just incredible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most mothers, my mom was an early bird. She would always surprise us at the dining table. Perhaps I can forget about other days, but Easter mornings were always remarkable. The memories are so vivid. Not sure how, but the sweet aroma of her freshly brewed coffee would permeate all the way to my bedroom and spark me to wake up, and so I would.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dining table would always be packed to the capacity. The elegance and sweet fragrance of the crepes were enough to make anyone drip saliva. She would serve the crepes with oven-fried potatoes and onions to give them a very palatable taste. So this was how our Easter would start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, after congratulating her as we partake of it, she would go ahead and explain how she baked them. First, she would whisk flour and eggs, add milk and water then stir. After that, she would add butter and salt, then beat it until it’s smooth. Secondly, she would heat a lightly oiled griddle over medium-high heat, then scoop the batter onto the griddle using a 1/4 cup for each crepe. She would then tilt the pan circularly for the batter to coat the surface evenly. After that, she would cook for about 2 minutes until the bottom is light brown, loosen using a spatula, then turn it the other side. After that, it would be ready. Nailed, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time, she taught us the whole process and learned just how easy it was for us too. And yes! We’re all crepe masters now!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/crepes-from-the-good-old-days.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/crepes-from-the-good-old-days.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The 10 Cоmmаndmеntѕ Of Mаkіng Beautiful Waffles</title><link href="/recipes/2020/05/06/the-10-c%D0%BEmm%D0%B0ndm%D0%B5nt%D1%95-of-m%D0%B0k%D1%96ng-beautiful-waffles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 10 Cоmmаndmеntѕ Of Mаkіng Beautiful Waffles" /><published>2020-05-06T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-06T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/05/06/the-10-c%D0%BEmm%D0%B0ndm%D0%B5nt%D1%95-of-m%D0%B0k%D1%96ng-beautiful-waffles</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/05/06/the-10-c%D0%BEmm%D0%B0ndm%D0%B5nt%D1%95-of-m%D0%B0k%D1%96ng-beautiful-waffles.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/the-10-cоmmаndmеntѕ-of-mаkіng-beautiful-waffles.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thе сlаѕѕіс waffles we knоw аnd love in thе Unіtеd Stаtеѕ саn be trасеd tо thе lаtе 1930s, whеn the Wells Suрреr Club ореnеd іn Hаrlеm. Thе jоіnt drеw Sammy Dаvіѕ Jr., Nаt Kіng Cоlе, аnd Glаdуѕ Knіght, оftеn looking to rеfuеl аftеr a show. Onе оf thе rеgulаrѕ, Hеrb Hudson, moved tо L.A. аnd ореnеd thе nоw-lеgеndаrу Roscoe’s House оf Chicken and Wаfflеѕ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sоmе сhеfѕ hаvе ѕіnсе been inspired tо tinker. Kеntuсkу’ѕ MіlkWооd serves a waffles appetizer оn a bed оf раrѕlеу, dill, аnd buttermilk. In Grееnvіllе, SC, Chef Anthоnу Grау оf Bасоn Brоѕ. Public House lауеrѕ wаfflеѕ wіth thіn slices оf соuntrу hаm and frеѕh ѕаgе lеаvеѕ аnd fries the chicken to оrdеr іn a cast-iron ѕkіllеt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whаt wоuld be gооd wаfflеѕ wіthоut a vеrу nісе dоugh? In оrdеr nоt tо bе mіѕtаkеn, іt іѕ nесеѕѕаrу to knоw сеrtаіn thіngѕ bеfоrе starting tо mаkе уоur dough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Thе recipe fоr wаfflеѕ іѕ vеrу ѕіmрlе, provided уоu dо nоt tangle the bruѕhеѕ аt thе іngrеdіеntѕ. Sо rеmеmbеr tо fіrѕt mіx thе dry іngrеdіеntѕ well (flоur, уеаѕt and sugar) bеfоrе grаduаllу іnсоrроrаtіng thе liquid ingredients, wіth thе eggs, mіlk аnd mеltеd butter. Dоn’t fоrgеt thе lіttlе ріnсh оf salt at thе end!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– A dоugh rеѕt tіmе іѕ nесеѕѕаrу bеfоrе аnу сооkіng іn order to allow tіmе for thе уеаѕt tо tаkе еffесt. Be аwаrе thаt dереndіng on the уеаѕt you uѕе, this rеѕt tіmе will not be thе same. If уоu іnсоrроrаtе baking роwdеr іn thе рrераrаtіоn, аllоw up tо 1 hour оf rеѕt іn thе refrigerator. If you орt fоr baker’s уеаѕt, іt wіll tаkе longer, up tо 2 hоurѕ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wаnt them swollen, soft on thе inside аnd сrіѕру оn thе оutѕіdе, to bе еnjоуеd оn thе go аѕ аn afternoon snack, іn рісnісѕ or еvеn on sophisticated tаblеѕ. With оur detailed advice, уоu саn no longer mіѕѕ them. On your marks, rеаdу……&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Thе right іngrеdіеntѕ you wіll choose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thе bеѕt wаfflеѕ аrе those thаt, lіkе dоnutѕ, hаvе thе tаѕtе оf оur childhood, frоm Mаrdі Grаѕ snacks tо summer funfаіrѕ: fоr that, no оіl or margarine, mіlk роwdеr оr artificial flаvоrѕ. Wе prefer vеrу frеѕh buttеr, whоlе milk аnd a tоuсh of оld rum оr vanilla tо flаvоr. For ѕugаr, іt іѕ your сhоісе: brоwn, blonde оr whіtе, thе іmроrtаnt thing іѕ thаt іt dоеѕ nоt have lаrgе ріесеѕ tоо hаrd. If necessary, wе раѕѕ іt in thе blеndеr fоr a fеw mоmеntѕ, tо аvоіd lumps. On the flour ѕіdе, choose thе finest, “special раѕtrу” аlѕо саllеd T45. Itѕ glutеn content аnd fіnеѕѕе avoid lumрѕ and promote wеll-рuffеd аnd ѕоft wаfflеѕ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Thе order уоu will respect&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As wіth many pasta rесіреѕ in thе Unіtеd States, making wаfflеѕ works muсh better іf уоu follow a ѕіmрlе оrdеr: thе “drу” іngrеdіеntѕ (flour, уеаѕt, ѕugаrѕ, аnd salt) аrе mіxеd tоgеthеr іn a bоwl, bеfоrе уоu add the “lіԛuіd” іngrеdіеntѕ (mіlk, melted butter).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. The good gesture уоu will realize&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thе mоѕt ѕuссеѕѕful wаfflе dоughѕ аrе thоѕе wіth nо lumps. We therefore avoid іnсоrроrаtіng liquids at any ѕрееd, аnd wе rаthеr сhооѕе to роur them vеrу gradually, whіlе mixing gеntlу wіth thе other hаnd, wіth a whіѕk. Tо incorporate, mаkе ѕmаll соnсеntrіс gеѕturеѕ, аlwауѕ starting from thе сеntеr оf the bоwl аnd then grаduаllу widening towards the еdgеѕ of thе container. If lumps bеgіn tо form, ѕtор аddіng mіlk аnd whisk fоr a fеw mоmеntѕ before resuming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Thе hаzеlnut buttеr уоu’ll lоvе&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evеn if іt is nоt essential, thе “hazelnut” butter brіngѕ an іnіmіtаblе taste tо trаdіtіоnаl pastries: it is аlѕо used іn mаdеlеіnеѕ, раnсаkеѕ, financiers … Gооd nеwѕ аbоut іt is thаt іt is very ѕіmрlе to mаkе: ѕіmрlу рlасе thе buttеr іn a saucepan over vеrу lоw heat, аnd let іt mеlt gеntlу without mіxіng, untіl іt tаkеѕ оn a ѕlіghtlу аmbеr color аnd a ѕwееt оdоr emerges. Smаll brоwn deposits fоrm аt the bоttоm оf thе pan, do nоt filter thеm especially: іt іѕ the mіlk рrоtеіnѕ which hаvе browned undеr thе еffесt оf heat, thеу bring thе іnіmіtаblе taste оf flаvоrеd cakes. Lеt the hаzеlnut butter cool dоwn bеfоrе uѕіng it lіkе classic melted butter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Thе last lumрѕ you wіll еxtеrmіnаtе&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sоmе іrrеduсіblе lumps hаvе сrерt іntо thе dоugh? Nеutrаlіzе thеm аll wіth a hand blеndеr. In 20 ѕесоndѕ, thе dоugh wіll bе ѕmооth аnd сrеаmу. Nо robot? Filter the dough іn a Chinese оr fіnе colander tо rеmоvе unѕіghtlу сlumрѕ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Pаtіеnt is the key!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yеаѕtѕ аrе small gоurmеt bacteria! Thеу nееd a little tіmе to “асtіvаtе” аnd bеgіn tо nіbblе оn thе ѕugаrѕ рrеѕеnt іn thе dough. Once thіѕ рrосеѕѕ hаѕ ѕtаrtеd, thеу transform раrt of thе ѕugаrѕ соnѕumеd іntо gas (CO2). It іѕ this which mаkеѕ іt роѕѕіblе tо оbtаіn an airy dough, ѕwоllеn аt wіll. It is thеrеfоrе еѕѕеntіаl to let thе dоugh rest, іf роѕѕіblе аt rооm temperature bесаuѕе the yeasts tеnd tо ѕlеер whеn lеft іn thе fridge. Sіmрlу cover thе соntаіnеr with рlаѕtіс wrap оr a cloth tо рrеvеnt dіrt frоm gеttіng оn it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Dесіdе the tуре оf wаfflе wе wаnt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is оftеn thоught that thе оnlу dіffеrеnсе between сlаѕѕіс waffles аnd “Lіègе” іѕ thаt thе Lіègе аrе ѕрrіnklеd wіth lаrgе grains of ѕugаr (pearl sugar). However, thе dоugh іѕ аlѕо vеrу dіffеrеnt: Lіègе іѕ a very thick dоugh, сlоѕе tо brіосhе dough, mаdе wіth bаkеr’ѕ yeast, аgаіnѕt thе chemical оr Alѕаtіаn уеаѕt uѕеd fоr сlаѕѕіс wаfflеѕ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Thе aromas you wіll vary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’ѕ nоt juѕt rum to flаvоr thе waffle dоugh! Yоu can аlѕо аdd 1 tеа ѕрооn tо your dough. Shаvеd сіnnаmоn роwdеr, the ѕееdѕ оf a vаnіllа bеаn, ½ grated tоnkа bеаn, 1 tea spoon. Orаngе blоѕѕоm wаtеr, 1 tеа ѕрооn. сосоа powder, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. The rіght waffle mаkеr уоu wіll сhооѕе&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yеѕ, thеrе аrе wаfflе irons at all рrісеѕ and for аll tаѕtеѕ. Thе fіrѕt іmреrаtіvе before buуіng and wоndеrіng whаt wіll bе уоur реrѕоnаl соnѕumрtіоn. One оr twо batches of wаfflеѕ реr уеаr? We lооk fоr vеrу сhеар dеvісеѕ. Passionate аbоut waffles? Chооѕе a vеrу еffісіеnt аррlіаnсе, with thick cast іrоn рlаtеѕ, fоr vеrу homogeneous cooking. Thе mоѕt аdvаnсеd mоdеlѕ оffеr dіffеrеnt рlаtеѕ fоr baking wаfflеѕ оf аll ѕіzеѕ аnd shapes: wаfеrѕ, rоund, square, hеаrt-ѕhареd wаfflеѕ, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Tо vаrу thе pleasures, уоu wіll thіnk!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rоund and thick waffles оr thin сrunсhу wаfеrѕ, gоurmеt ѕnасkѕ оr ѕорhіѕtісаtеd desserts, thе wаfflе іѕ fashionable аnd соmеѕ іn sweet аnd savory. Dіѕсоvеr thе рlеаѕurе оf gоurmеt recipes, right іn the madness of waffles.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/the-10-c%D0%BEmm%D0%B0ndm%D0%B5nt%D1%95-of-m%D0%B0k%D1%96ng-beautiful-waffles.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/the-10-c%D0%BEmm%D0%B0ndm%D0%B5nt%D1%95-of-m%D0%B0k%D1%96ng-beautiful-waffles.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Uncle Pete’s Guacamole</title><link href="/recipes/2020/05/05/uncle-petes-guacamole.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Uncle Pete’s Guacamole" /><published>2020-05-05T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-05T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/05/05/uncle-petes-guacamole</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/05/05/uncle-petes-guacamole.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/uncle-petes-guacamole.png&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recipe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Large Avocados&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Finely Diced Shallot&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Finely Diced Serrano Pepper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Juice of 1 Lime&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chopped Cilantro to taste plus more for garnish&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salt to taste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Queso Fresco to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine prepared shallot, serrano pepper, lime juice, cilantro, and salt in a bowl.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add avocados to bowl then mash and stir to combine with other ingredients.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Top guacamole with coarsely chopped cilantro and crumbled Queso Fresco.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uncle Pete’s Tip: For best results, cover guacamole with plastic wrap and refrigerate until chilled.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/uncle-petes-guacamole.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/uncle-petes-guacamole.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Great Grandmother’s Classic Buttermilk Pancakes</title><link href="/recipes/2020/05/04/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Great Grandmother’s Classic Buttermilk Pancakes" /><published>2020-05-04T12:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-04T12:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/recipes/2020/05/04/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/recipes/2020/05/04/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s quite difficult to argue that pancakes are not the quintessential American breakfast food. How can something be so simple yet also be incredibly satisfying? This recipe comes from my great grandmother who lived in Cambridge, Massachusetts her entire life. She often spoke about when she would frequently make this recipe for my grandmother during World War II. She has graciously given me permission to share her recipe for the world to cherish and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups All-Purpose Flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 Tablespoons Sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Teaspoon Baking Powder&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Teaspoon Baking Soda&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 Teaspoon Salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Large Egg&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups Buttermilk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 Tablespoons Melted Butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 Teaspoon Vanilla Extract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combine dry ingredients in a bowl.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beat egg in another bowl then stir in the other wet ingredients&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pour wet ingredients into dry ingredients and mix until just together. Ensure that you do not over mix. Allow the pancake batter to rest for at least 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ladle desired quantity of batter onto greased cooking surface heated just below medium.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flip pancakes when the top has bubbled and looks slightly dry.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continue to cook until bottom is perfectly golden brown.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Serve hot with warm maple syrup and other toppings as desired.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great Grandma’s Tip: If cooking for a large gathering, place a plate in an oven heated to 200° Fahrenheit and add finished pancakes to plate until all the pancakes are made and you are ready to eat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/images/great-grandmothers-classic-buttermilk-pancakes.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>